Daniel Yankelovich Papers
© 2002 University of Connecticut
- Series VI: Mary Komarnicki Yankelovich,1937-1993
  - Subseries A: Projects, undated, 1937-1991
    - Coming To Public Judgment: Making Democracy Work in a Complex World, 1991
      - Typescript draft D, edited
        - Chapter D1A " A Missing Concept", 1989 Jul 6 (Box 96:2228)
        - Chapter D1B "What is Quality in Public Opinion?", 1989 Jul 12 (Box 96:2229)
      - Typescript Draft, Chapter 11 "The Cold War: End it or Not?," edited, [1988-1989] (Box 96:2230)
      - Manuscript pieces, edited: miscellaneous, [1988-1989] (Box 96:2231)
      - Invitee list - Lubin House reception, 1991 Apr-May (Box 97:2232)
    - A Compendium of Poll Data on Health - draft, 1988 Nov (Box 97:2233-2236)
    - A Compendium of Poll Data on Health - excerpts, 1988 Nov (Box 97:2237)
    - The Holocaust and the Media Conference, 1988 May 19
      - Conference information, 1988 (Box 97:2238)
      - Yankelovich, D. and Mary Komarnicki, " American Public Opinion of Holocaust Events: 1933-1945", 1988 (Box 97:2239)
      - Yankelovich, D., "German Behavior, American Attitudes," Dimensions, vol. 4, no. 3, 1988 (Box 97:2240)
      - Research data, 1938-1948 (Box 97:2241)
    - GlobeTrends 1990 - Strategies for a Global Economy (S.A.G.E.) Presentation
      - (SEE ALSO: boxes 72-73)
      - Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 97:2242)
      - Meeting notes, 1990 (Box 97:2243-2245)
      - GlobeTrends 1990 Presentation of Services, edited, 1990 (Box 97:2246)
      - "S.A.G.E. presentation" - draft, 1990 Jan 21 (Box 97:2247)
      - "S.A.G.E. presentation" - draft, [1990] (Box 97:2248)
      - GlobeTrends 1990 - draft, edited, 1990 Jan 26 (Box 97:2249)
      - GlobeTrends 1990 - draft, edited, 1990 Mar 2 (Box 97:2250)
      - GlobeTrends 1990 - draft, 1990 Mar 6 (Box 97:2251)
      - GlobeTrends 1990 - draft, 1990 Mar 12 (Box 97:2252)
      - Slide/page layout - draft 1, 1990 (Box 97:2253)
      - Slide/page layout - draft 1, edited, 1990 (Box 97:2254)
      - Slide/page layout - draft 2, edited, 1990 (Box 97:2255)
      - Slide/page layout - draft 2, edited, 1990 (Box 97:2256)
      - Slide/page layout - draft 3, 1990 (Box 97:2257)
      - Slide/page layout - draft 3, edited, 1990 (Box 97:2258)
      - Slide/page layout - draft 4, 1990 (Box 98:2259)
      - GlobeTrends 1990 (unbound), 1990 (Box 98:2260-2261)
      - GlobeTrends 1990 - Selected Excerpts - master copy, 1990 (Box 98:2262)
      - GlobeTrends 1990: slides, [1990] (Box 98:2263)
      - GlobeTrends 1990: computer disks, [1990] (Box 98:2264)
      - Additional pages: miscellaneous, [1990] (Box 98:2265)
      - Additional slide/page layouts and pages, [1990] (Box 98:2266)
      - GlobeTrends 1991 - slide/page layout, [1991] (Box 98:2267)
      - Age Wave, Inc., "Aging America: The Shape of Things to Come" - slide presentation, undated (Box 98:2268)
    - "Roper Analysis for Project Dialogue", [2983] (Box 98:2269-2270)
    - Academic Projects
      - "When Rumor Becomes Reliable: The Divergent Social Processing of Information", [1980-1982] (Box 98:2271)
      - "Rumor Transmission: An Ecological Perspective", 1980 (Box 98:2272)
      - "Sick Role: A Definition and Construct Critique", 1981 (Box 98:2273)
      - "The Perceived Severity Symptom Standard: A Prerequisite for Helpseeking Behavior", 1981 (Box 98:2274)
      - "Predictors of Formal and Informal Psychological Helpseeking in a Metropolitan Community" - draft master's thesis, 1982 Oct (Box 98:2275-2276)
      - "Predictors of Formal and Informal Psychological Helpseeking in a Metropolitan Community" - master's thesis, 1982 Nov (Box 98:2277-2278)
      - Ibid, including abstract and reference sections, 1983 (Box 99:2279-2281)
      - Thesis notes, [1982-1983] (Box 99:2282-2286)
      - Job search, 1982-1983 (Box 99:2287-2288)
  - Subseries B: Related Material, n.d, 1958-1993
    - The AEI Economist - newsletters, 1989 Apr-Jul (Box 99:2289)
    - Boardroom Reports, vol. 18 no. 1, 1989 Jan (Box 99:2290)
    - Books
      - Bryant, Barbara Everitt, American Women Today and Tomorrow, 1977 (Box 99:2291)
      - Goodman, John L., Jr., Public Opinion During the Reagan Administration, 1983 (Box 99:2292)
      - Masnick, George and Mary Jo Bane, The Nation's Families: 1960-1990, 1980 (Box 99:2293)
      - U.S. Department of Education, Office of Educational Research and Improvement, Youth Indicators 1988, 1988 (Box 99:2294)
      - Ornstein, Norman, Andrew Kohut and Larry McCarthy, The People, The Press, and Politics, 1985 (Box 99:2295)
      - Rielly, John, ed.American Public Opinion and U.S. Foreign Policy 1983, 1983 (Box 99:2296)
      - Roper Organization, Inc., The American Circle Youth Poll, 1988 (Box 99:2297)
    - Birth statistics, 1981 (Box 99:2298)
    - Family, undated, 1991 (Box 100:2299)
    - Family - public opinion data, 1962-1990 (Box 100:2300-2301)
    - Funeral speech for Henry Kent: handwritten draft by D. Yankelovich, 1982 (Box 100:2302)
    - Glenn, Norval, "The Family Values of Americans", [1990] (Box 100:2303)
    - Miscellaneous, 1987-1991 (Box 100:2304)
    - Miscellaneous: charts, tables, and notes, 1991 (Box 100:2305)
    - Miscellaneous: polls, 1980-1988 (Box 100:2306)
    - Pluralism, 1958-1991 (Box 100:2307)
    - POLL (Public Opinion Location Library)
      - User's Manual, 1987 (Box 100:2308)
      - POLL (newsletter) vol. 1, no. 1, vol. 2, nos. 1-3, vol. 3, no. 1, 1987-1989 (Box 100:2309)
      - POLL search for the Public Agenda Foundation, 1993 (Box 100:2310)
      - Notes, undated (Box 100:2311)
    - Schudson, Michael, " The News Media and the Democratic Process": draft WYE paper, 1982 Sep (Box 100:2312)
    - Self-confidence: public opinion data, 1988 (Box 100:2313)
    - Stage fright survey, undated (Box 100:2314)
    - Wellington Management Co., Future Themes (Box 100:2315)
    - Yankelovich D., "The Foreign Policy Mandate: Regaining Control Abroad - Table 1", 1981 Mar 30 (Box 100:2316)
    - Council for Advancement and Support of Education, Annual Report, 1985-1986 (Box 100:2317)
    - YSW, Sex Stereotypes and Candidacy for High Level Political Office, 1984 (Box 100:2318)
    - Yankelovich, D., "Work, Values and the New Breed", 1978 (Box 100:2319)
    - Dartmouth Conference XVI
      - (SEE ALSO: boxes 39-41)
      - Stenographic record, 1988 Apr 25-29 (Box 100:2319)
      - D. Yankelovich notes, 1988 (Box 100:2319)